<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HarvardMuseums</string>

    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email completions."</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>

    <!--Aqui se coloca o id pego no site developers.facebook >> O código do site já vem setado com o id-->
    <string name="facebook_app_id">295659717955281</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb295659717955281</string>

    <string name="exhibition_detail">




        Animal-Shaped Vessels from the Ancient World: Feasting with Gods, Heroes, and Kings brings
        together nearly 60 elaborate vessels of animal shape from collections in the United States
        and Europe. While the songs, speeches, and prayers that enlivened ancient feasts are now
        largely lost to us, these vessels have survived, offering a glimpse into the rich symbolism
        and communal practices that found expression at these gatherings. Taking animal-shaped vessels
        as performative props in the multifaceted world of feasting, the exhibition not only introduces
        the social and ceremonial functions of these ritual occasions, but also highlights the essential
        and universal role played by food and drink—and by the highly imaginative containers used to
        enjoy these refreshments.

        The exhibition includes vessels in the shape of standing or reclining animals, animal-headed
        cups and beakers, drinking horns, and animated pitchers. Various creatures, real and imagined,
        give these objects their shapes: powerful bulls and rams, majestic lions and mythical griffins,
        wild boars and goats, deer and gazelles, graceful birds, and braying donkeys, among others.
        Assembling such a range of vessels for the first time, the exhibition presents a cross-cultural
        and cross-disciplinary examination of how they spanned geography and time, across three
        continents and over three millennia. The international menagerie of drinking and pouring
        vessels vividly illustrates not just how shapes and artistic forms crossed borders, but how
        ideas as well were exchanged among cultures—tangible evidence of close contact and the
        intermingling of traditions.

    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
